Guide to the Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records, 1964-1978 and undated RL.00405
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. records
1941-1978 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Foote, Cone & Belding
RL.00405
869
6 Linear Feet
The Foote, Cone & Belding advertising agency (FCB) was formed in 1942 when Albert Lasker sold the Lord & Thomas agency to three of his executives. A pioneer in television advertising, FCB later merged with Draft Direct Worldwide to become Draftfcb, a subsidiary of The Interpublic Group, and one of the largest advertising agencies in the United States. The Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records span the years 1964-1978 and consists of audiotapes, videocassettes, 16mm film, focus group studies, television schedules, scripts and photoboards from television commercials. Clients include Armour-Dial, Burger King, Hormel, Interstate Brands (Wonder Bread), Johnson & Johnson, Kraft, Pizza Hut, McDonald's, S.C. Johnson, Sears & Roebuck, Western Electric, and Zenith. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as gifts in 1993 and 2002.
Historical Note
Missing Title
1873 The Lord & Thomas Agency founded
1942 Albert Lasker retires and sells L&T to executives Emerson Foote, Fairfax Cone and Don Belding
1962 Foote, Cone & Belding becomes a publicly traded corporation
1994 Foote, Cone & Belding renamed True North Communications
2001 The Interpublic Group of Companies buys True North Communications and restores the name Foote, Cone & Belding
2006 Foote, Cone & Belding merges with Draft Direct Worldwide to become Draftfcb
Sources: Encyclopedia of Chicago entry on Foote Cone & Belding; Adbrands entry on Draftfcb.
Collection Overview
The Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records span the years 1964-1978 and consists of audiotapes, videocassettes, 16mm film, focus group studies, television schedules, scripts and photoboards from television commercials. Clients include Armour-Dial, Burger King, Hormel, Interstate Brands (Wonder Bread), Johnson & Johnson, Kraft, Pizza Hut, McDonald's, S.C. Johnson, Sears & Roebuck, Western Electric, and Zenith.
Collection Arrangement
Collection is arranged into four series: General Files; Photoboards; Scripts; and Audiovisual Materials.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives held in the Hartman Center:
Anthony Viola Papers
Dan Seymour Papers
John F. Devine Papers
Lois Gaeta Papers
Maury Holland Papers
Ron Kaatz Papers
In addition, related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Jim Varney Collection of Advertising
John Benjamin Harris Papers
Television commercials; Advertising agencies; Storyboards; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Audiotapes; Videocassettes; Television scripts; 16mm; Burger King Corporation; Armour-Dial, Inc; Foote, Cone & Belding; Western Electric Company; McDonald's Corporation; Zenith Electric Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Hormel Foods Corporation; Kraft Foods Company; Johnson & Johnson Baby Products Company
- General Files, 1941-1978, 301540; 1 box
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes communication and focus group studies, corporate library guide, and television schedules. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Commercial lists from videotapes, 1977-1978, 301545 (Box 1)
  - Communications Study--Zenith Radio Group, 1976, 301544 (Box 1)
  - Corporate Library-Guide to the FCB Information Center, 1978 May, 301543 (Box 1)
  - Focus groups, 1976, 301542; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Televisions schedules, 1977, 301541 (Box 1)
  - Fels-Naptha advertising displays and designs, 1941-1942 and undated (Box 7)
    Scope and Contents
    Posters, display banners and print advertising portfolios, along with some drawings for advertisements signed by Norman Coe, an Art Director at FCB in the 1940s.
- Photoboards, 1964-1978, 301514; 3 boxes
  Includes original and aired photoboards, frames of television commercials. Aired photoboards include locations, date, and programming information.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged alphabetically by product type, then by products. Variations in spelling reflect variations in the files.
  - Antacids, 1975-1978, 301539 (Box 1)
    [Includes Alka 2, Alka-Seltzer, Bisodol Tablets, Brioschi, Conquel, Di-gel, Eno, Formula 1447 Antacid Demulcant, Kaopectate, Maalox, Pepto-Bismol, Phillips Antacid Tablets, Remegel, Rolaids, Seltzer 2000, Tempo, Tums, Willard's]
  - Aspirin and substitutes, 1974-1978, 301538 (Box 1)
    [Includes Anacin, Aspergum, Bayer, BC Powder, Bufferin, Congespirin, Datril, Excedrin, Liquiprin, St. Joseph's, Trilium, Tylenol, Vanquish, Viro-med].
  - Baby products, 1964-1975, 301537 (Box 1)
    [Includes babyScott Diapers, Curity Tape Tab Disposable Diapers, Dy-Dee Diaper Service, Gerber Baby Food, Johnson's Disposable Diapers, Johnson's Baby Bath, Pampers, Wet Ones]
  - Beverages, 1975-1975, 301536 (Box 1)
    [Includes 7 Up, Anheuser Busch Natural Light Beer, Budweiser, Community Iced Tea, Country Time, Dr. Pepper, Folger's Coffee, Gatorade, Kool-aid, Lipton, General Foods Mellow Roast Coffee, Michelob Beer, Miller Beer, Mogen David Premium Wines, Nestea, Ocean Spray, Old Milwaukee Beer, Orange Crush, Pabst Blue Ribbon Beer, Red Rose Tea, Salada Tea, Sanka, Schaefer Beer, Schlitz Beer, Tang, Tetley Tea, Welch's, Wyler's]
  - Bread, 1974-1975, 301535 (Box 1)
    [Includes Butternut, Earth Grains Old Fashioned, Fresh & Natural Wheat, Hart's, Homepride, Millbrook, Nolde, Old Home, Sunbeam, Weber's, Wonder]
  - Condiments, sauces, spreads, oils, 1975-1975, 301534 (Box 1)
    [Includes A1 Steak Sauce, Betty Crocker Bac-Os Bacon Bits, Blue Bonnet Smooth & Easy Gravy, Byron's Bar-B-Q Sauce, C and H Sugar, Cool Whip Topping, Creative Kitchens Smooth & Easy Brown Gravy Maker, Crystal Barbeque Sauce, Dream Whip Whipped Topping Mix, Durkee Chris' & Pitt's Hot Bar-B-Q Sauce, Jiff, Kraft Barbecue Sauce, Lipton's Lite Lunch Soup Mix, Maull's Barbecue Sauce, Mazola Corn Oil, Mrs. Filberts Corn Oil Spread, Ocean Spray Country Girl Grilling Sauce, Open Pit Barbecue Sauce, Peter Pan Peanut Butter, Shake 'n Bake Barbecue Mix, Skippy Peanut Butter, Smucker's Grape Jelly, Squeeze 'n Season Cooking & Grilling Sauce, Wright's Liquid Smoke]
  - Cough suppressants, 1972-1976, 301533 (Box 1)
    [Includes Benylin Cough Syrup, Breacol, Cheracol D, Children's Hold 4 Hour Cough Suppressant, Creomulsion, Halls Mentho-lyptus, Hold 4 Hour Cough Suppressant, Listerine Lozenges, Luden's Menthol Cough Drops, Mentholatum Ointment, Nyquil, Pertussin 8 Hour, Romilar, Scot-Tussin, Silence is Golden Formula, Sucrets Lozenges, Vaporizer in a Bottle, Vick's Cough Drops, Vicks, Victor]
  - Dairy and margarine, 1975-1978, 301532 (Box 2)
    [Includes Blue Bonnet, Borden, Chiffon, Dannon Danny Frozen Yogurt, Fleischmann's, Imperial, Kraft, Knudsen, Mazola, Parkay, Price's Ice Cream, Promise, Yonson Yogurt, Yoplait]
  - Decongestants and antihistamines, 1974-1977, 301531 (Box 2)
    [Includes 4 Way Nasal Spray, Allerest Hay Fever Reliever, A.R.M Allergy Relief Medicine, Bayer, Congespirin, Conquel, Contact, Doktors Nasal Spray, Dristan, Neo-synephrine, Sinarest, Sine-Aid, Sine-Off, Sinutab, St. Joseph's, Vicks]
  - Electronics, 1977-1978, 301530 (Box 2)
    [Includes Western Electric, Zenith]
  - Floor and bathroom cleaners, 1974-1978, 301529 (Box 2)
    [Includes 20 Mule Power Bathroom Cleaner, Picam 120 Day Automatic Bowl Cleaner, Aerex, Aerowax, Beacon Blue, Blu Boy, Bowlene, Clean & Clear, Depend-O, Dow Sponge on Bathroom Cleaner, Fresh n' Clean, Future, Lysol, Mop & Glo Floor Wax, Mr. Clean, Pine-Sol, Refresh, Sani Flush, Sani-foam Instant Bathroom Cleaner, Scott Liquid Gold, Sno Bowl, Spic and Span, Step Saver, Top Job, Ty-D-Bol, Vanish, Whip Cap Pine Oil Cleaner]
  - Furniture polish and carpet cleaners, 1975-1977, 301528 (Box 2)
    [Includes Austin's Carpet Cleaner, Behold Furniture Wax, Bissell Rug Shampoo, Blue Luster Carpet Shampoo, Clean Sweep Rug Cleaner, Endust, Favor Furniture Polish, Fresh Look Vacuum Helper, Formula 10 Rug and Carpet Cleaner, Gloss 'n Toss, HR Carpet Cleaner, Old English, Penthouse Furniture Polish, Pledge, Rinse N Vac, Rug Doctor, Spray 'n Vac, Steamex, Tuxton, Victory Miracle Polishing Cloth, Weiman Furniture Creme, Woolite Rug Cleaner]
  - Home and automobile care, 1976-1977, 301527 (Box 2)
    [Includes Armstrong Flooring, S.C. Johnson Sprint, Sherwin-Williams Paint, Speed Queen Washers and Dryers, Sunbeam]
  - Insecticide, 1976-1978, 301526 (Box 2)
    [Includes Off!, Raid]
  - Laundry: detergents and bleaches, 1974-1978, 301525 (Box 2)
    [Includes Ajax, All, Arm & Hammer, Austin's A-1 Bleach, Axion, Biz, Bold, Borateem, Cheer, Clorox, Dynamo, Ego, Eno, Era, Fab, Javex Bleach, Linco Bleach, Miracle White, Roman Bleach, Switch Liquid Bleach Substitute, Tide, Woolite]
  - Laundry: prewashes, additives, softeners, 1975-1977, 301524 (Box 2)
    [Includes Allways Soft, Bounce, Calgon Cling Free, Downy, Easy Out Stain Remover, Fantastik, Faultless Spray Pre-Wash, Final Touch, Fleecy Fabric, Hi-Lex Lemon Plus Fabric Softener, Kuf 'n Kolar (Cuff & Collar) Stain Remover, Lestoil, Magic Liquid Prewash, Miracle White, Rave Detergent Booster, Rain Barrel, Shout, Spray 'n Wash, Sta-Puf Fabric Softener, Terrific Laundry Soil & Stain Remover, Texize All Ways Soft Fabric Softener, Washable Stain Kit, Whoosh Stain Remover, Wish]
  - Meats, 1975-1978, 301523 (Box 2)
    [Includes Ashmore, Austex Chili, Austin's Sausage (in can), Ballard's Honey B Farm Sausage, Betty Crocker Meat Flavored Sticks, Blue Ribbon Smoked Sausage, Bob Evans Sausage, Bryan Sausage, Clark Beef Stew, Copeland Pork Sausage, Dennison's Chili, Deli-loaf, Eckrich, Edwards' Sausage, Field Country Sausage, Foster Farms Chicken, Frey Farm Brand Sausage, Gebhardts Chili, Gianelli Sausage, Gold Star Chili, Gooch German Sausage, Hickory Farms Beef Stick, Hillshire Farms Sausage, Hormel (Spam, Dinty Moore), Jimmy Dean Sausage, Johnsonville Country Sausage, Libby's Canned Meat, Lipton Make a Better Burger, Mayrose Brown 'n Serve Sausage, Morningstar Farms, Nalley's Chili, Oscar Mayer, Owens Country Sausage, Parrot Meats, Protein-ettes Vegetable Protein, RB Rice Sausage, Rudy Sausage, Safeway Trophy Brand Beef Patty Mix, Schweigert Supper Sausage, Shelly Brand Pure Pork Sausage, Stagg Chili, Stokes Chili, Swift Brown 'n Serve Sausage, Tennessee Pride, Thielmann's Old Wisconsin Sausage, Treet, Underwood Spreads, Van Camp's Chilee Weenee, Vietti Chili, Webber's, Wilson's Canned Meats, Wolf Brand Chili]
  - Miscellaneous medicine, 1974-1976, 301522 (Box 2)
    [Includes Desenex, Freezone, Geritol, Head Start Vitamins for Hair, NP 27, One a Day Vitamins, Unicap]
  - Restaurants and fast food, 1974-1976, 301521 (Box 2)
    [Includes Arby's, Bonanza Steak House, Burger Chef, Burger King, Dairy Queen, El Chico Restaurant, Gino's Restaurant, H. Salt Fish & Chips, Hardee's, Jack-in-the-Box, Kentucky Fried Chicken, La Pizzeria, McDonald's, Pasquale's Pizza, Pizza Hut, Pizza Inn, Red Barn Restaurants, Red Lobster, Rustler Steak House, Shakey's Pizza, Straw Hat Pizza Palace, Village Inn Pizza Parlor]
  - Retailers, 1974-1978, 301520 (Box 3)
    [Includes First National Bank of Chicago, Hallmark, Sears]
  - Shampoo and hair care products, A-H, 1975-1978, 301519 (Box 3)
    [Includes Adorn Hair Spray, Afro Sheen, Agree Creme Rinse, Alberto VO5, Apple Vinegar Shampoo, Dial II Dandruff Shampoo, Baby Magic Shampoo, Body & Spice Shampoo, Body on Tap, Breck, Capri, Clairol, Council, Denorex, Derlavon, Earth Born, Everynight, Gee Your Hair Smells Terrific, Gillette the Handler, Gray Drug Stores, Gray's Baby Shampoo, Halo, Head, Head & Shoulders, Helena Rubenstein, Helene Curtis]
  - Shampoo and hair care products, I-Z, 1974-1978, 301518 (Box 3)
    [Includes Intensive Care, Jhirmack, Johnson's Baby Shampoo, Lanocane Medicated, Life Brand, L'Oreal Hair Color, Markham Shampoo, Mennen Baby Magic, Noxema, Protein 21, Revlon, Selsun Blue, Style, Suave, Sunshine Harvest, Tegrin, Tru-Nature, Ultra Sheen, Vigorol Hair Relaxer, Vita-Fluff, Vitalis Super Hold Hair Spray, Wella-Balsam, White Rain, X-itch Shampoo]
  - Shoes, shoe stores, shoe inserts, 1975-1976, 301517 (Box 3)
    [Includes Adams, Adidas, Bata Tennis, Buster Brown, Cobbies, Converse, Dr. Scholl's, Fayva, Gillette Foot Guard, Goldblatt's, Goot, Guild House, Hill Brothers, Hush Puppies, Huston's, Jerry Shams, Jumping Jack, J.C. Penney, Karl's, Trophy, Keds, Kid Power, Kinney, Larry's, M&J Men's Store, Montgomery Ward, Neils Famous Footwear, Nelson, Nucon's, Payless, Peacock, Puma, Red Wing, Richway, Rinks, Shoe Rack, Sneaker Circus, Thom McAnn, Volume Shoes]
  - Snack foods, 1974-1978, 301516 (Box 3)
    [Includes 3 Musketeers, After Eight Wafer-Thin Chocolate Mints, Archway Cookies, Bachman Tor-Tico Tortilla Chips, Bosco Chocolate Syrup, Brach's Candy, California Strawberries, Caramels (Kraft), Chunky Candy, Dentyne Gum, Fritos, Forever Yours Candy Bar, Heath Bar, Heinz Deep Fries, Hershey, Jell-0 Instant Gelatin, Kit Kat Bar, Life Savers, Lowney, M&M Candy, Mars Bar, Mrs. Bumby's Potato Chips, Mrs. Goodcookie, Nabisco, Nestle's, Oh Henry!, Ovaltine, Owyhee Butter Toffee, Pacers Mint Chews, Pearson's Salted Nut Roll, Peter Paul Mounds, Pringles Potato Chips, Reese's Peanut Butter Cup, Rothchilds Candy, Skittles, Smuggler Candy Bar, Snickers Bar, Starburst, Sunkist, Tootsie Pop, Tootsie Roll, Turtles Candy, Washington State Apples, Western Family Potato Chips, Whitman's Sampler Chocolates]
  - Soap, skin care, deodorant, 1975-1978, 301515 (Box 3)
    [Includes Aapri Facial Cleanser, Arrid XX, Camay, Caress, Clearasil, Coast, Demassage Moisture Bar, Dial, Dove, Gentle Touch, Irish Spring, Ivory, Jean Nate, Jergens, Johnson's Baby, Lifebuoy, Lux, Multiscrub, Noxzema, Old Spice, P-300, Palmolive, Phisoderm, Roger Gallet, Run 'n Scrub, Safeguard, Stri-Dex Pads, Shield, Subtropic Tanning Lotion, Sundown Sunscreen, Tone, Touch of Sweden Hand Lotion, Village Bath Bubbles, Woodbury Nature Scents, Yardley, Zest]
- Scripts, 1977 and undated, 301491; 2 boxes
  Includes handwritten, original, and completed scripts of television commercials. Tape numbers are transcribed from the original folders; the tapes themselves do not reside in this collection.
  Arranged alphabetically by advertiser, then by script number. Variations in spelling reflect variations as written in the files.
  - CHF 1, 2, 3 handwritten with index, undated, 301513 (Box 3)
    [Includes Dial Soap, Hallmark, Johnson's (Raid, Off!, Shout), Speed Queen, Sears (Diehard Batteries, Motor Oil, Shock Absorbers, Tires), Wilton Cake Decorating Kit]
  - CHF 1, 2, 3 originals without index, undated, 301512 (Box 3)
    [Includes Dial Soap, Hallmark (Games, Gifts), Johnson's (Raid, Off!, Shout), Speed Queen, Sears, Wilton Cake Decorating Kit]
  - FCB Tape 1 corrected (almost perfect), with index, undated, 301511 (Box 3)
    [Includes 4-H Club, Anacin, Arby's, B.C. Powder, Beauty Mist, Close-up, Coffee Mate, Continental Mark V, Corningware, Covergirl Mascara, Cutlass, Dial Soap, Diet Pepsi, Doans Pills, Duration Nasal Spray, Exxon, Face Quencher, Feenamint, Ford, Friskie Dinners, Geritol, Golden Eagle Flour, Golden Griddle, Granola, Hanes, Holiday Inn, Holly Farms, Honeywell, Kellogg's Raisin Bran, Jaguar, Kit Kat, Jello Pudding, Lilly, Listerine, Maytag, McDonald's, Midland CB, Miss Clairol, MoCap, Morningstar Farms, Mr. Coffee, Mustang II, National Guard, Neese's Country Sausage, Orafix, Peter Pan, Pharmaceutical Manufacturer's Association, Pillsbury, Poligrip, Post Grape Nuts, Post Raisin Bran, Primatene Mist, Raleigh Savings, Schlitz, Sears Auto, Snackin' Cake, Stove Top Stuffing, Solo Dog Food, Sominex, Sucrets, Taster's Choice, Tiparillo, Thunderbird, Toyota, Trans South Mortgage, Underalls, Vaseline, Winn Dixie, Wrigley's Spearmint Gum, Zenith]
  - FCB Tape 2, originals with index, undated, 301510 (Box 3)
    [Includes Ajax, All-Good Aluminum Siding, Alexander Ford, Avis, Avon, Ban Roll-on, Big Mac, Breck (Creme Rinse, hair spray), Breyer's, British Sterling, Burger King, Car Quest, Cat Bus Service, Clorox II, Congespirin, Cricket Lighters, Datril 500, Dentu-Creme, Excedrin, Foot Joy, Fiat, Flintstone Vitamins, Gregory Poole Equipment, Hall's Mentho-Lyptus, Hamburger Helper, Holly Farms, Hunt's Prima Salsa, Jello Pudding, Kemper Insurance, Kodak, Kraft Mayonnaise, L'eggs, Lifebuoy, Lilly, Lipton Tea, Long Distance, May Queen, Mazola Margarine, Michelob, No Nonsense Pantyhose, Norelco Dial-a-Brew, Oh Henry!, Pabst, Palmolive, Pilot Life, Pledge, Preference, RCA, Redken, Ritz Crackers, Rosemilk, Roses, Soft & Dry Roll-on, Shell, Short and Sassy, Shredded Wheat, Singer, Skippy Peanut Butter, Spalding Golf Clubs, Special K, Sunbeam Bread, Tab, Total, Trans South Mortgage, Triscuits, Toyota, Volare, Wendy's, White Cloud, Windex, Winn Dixie, Wise Potato Chips, Wisk]
  - FCB Tape 3, originals with index, 523 missing undated, 301509 (Box 3)
    [Includes Ajax, Alka Seltzer, Allstate, American Express, American Motors, Arrid Roll-on, Autolite, Ban, Bayer, Ben-Gay, Betty Crocker, Blue Bonnet, British Sterling, Calgonite, Campbell's Soup, Certs, Cheerios, Cheetos, Crisco, Crop, Dentu-creme, Dristan, Easy Off, Edge, Fiat 131, Fit and Trim, Ford, Fram Air Filter, Golden Grahams, Goodrich Tires, Gualtney Hotdogs, Gulden's Mustard, Harley-Davidson, Honda Civic, Hoover Cleaners, HTH Chlorine, Hungry Jack, Hunt's Sloppy Joe, Jello Gelatin, Job Service Elderly, Kawasaki, Kleenex, Kraft, Kraft Miracle Whip, Lee Maci II, Listerine, Mennen Speed Stick, Michelin Tires, Mobil Oil, Mrs. Butterworth's Syrup, Nestea, Ocean Spray, Old English, Old Milwaukee, Parkay, Pampers, Peerless Faucets, Pepsi, Playtex, Polaroid, Polaroid Cool Ray, Radio Shack, Ragu, Reese's Peanut Butter Cups, Revlon, Reynolds Aluminum, Sanka, Savings and Loan, Schick, Schlitz, Schlitz Lite, Selsun Blue, Shout, Shredded Wheat, Squoze, Snack 'n Cake, Sominex, Stir 'n Frost, Stuart McGuire Catalog, Sure Anti-perspirant, Team, Tone, Toyota, United Airlines, Volkswagen, Water Pik, Wella Balsam, Wendy's, Wheat Chex, Wheaties, Whirlpool, Windex, Wrigley's Gum, Yamaka]
  - FCB Tape 4, originals with index, undated, 301508 (Box 4)
    [Includes Aftate, Aim, All, Allstate, Anacin, Avon, Band-Aid, Black Flag, Camay, Cheese Swirls, Chevrolet, Compound W, Corn Chex, Crest, Danny Frozen Yogurt, Dentu-creme, Desenex, Downy, Duke Power, Era, Ex Lax, FDA, Firestone, Ford Fordathon, Ford Mercury, Fresh Horizons, Friskie's Buffet, Gaines Burger, Gallo Red Rose, Geritol, Gleem, Glidden, Goodrich, Goodyear, Greyhound, Hardee's, Hartz 2-in-1 Collar, Hi-C, HR Carpet Cleaner, Jiff, Kodak, Kellogg's Corny Snacks, Kool Aid, Lanocaine, Lifesavers, Lipton, L'Oreal Preference, McDonald's, Metamucil, Minute Maid Lemonade, Montgomery Ward, Mountain Dew, Murine Ear Drops, Nacho Doritos, Nair, Neese, NC Opticians, Oscar Mayer, Outgrow, Pam, Pepsodent, Phillips Petroleum, Pillsbury Plus, Pizza Hut, Polaroid 1-Step, Prell, Preparation H, Raintree, Red and White Stores, Schaefer, Safeday, Schlitz, Sears, Sears Automotive Sale, Sherwin-Williams Latex, Short 'n Sassy, Soft and Pretty, Sominex, Sure, Taster's Choice, Total Cereal, Triumph Tr-7, Upjohn Kaopectate, Vaseline, Vim, Visa, Wachovia Teller II, Western Auto, Wilkinson II, Williams 'Lectric Shave, Winn Dixie, Wyler's]
  - FCB Tape 5, originals with index, undated, 301507 (Box 4)
    [Includes Alka Seltzer, Allstate, AMC Gremlin, Anacin, Arm & Hammer, Ban Basic, Bounce, Bufferin, Campbell's Chunky, Carnation Cat Food, Carefree Panty Shields, Carnation Friskies Dog Food, Carter's Infant Wear, Chevrolet Chevelle, Close Up Toothpaste, Cool Whip, Datril 500, Dow Bathroom Cleaner, Dristan, Elmer's Glue, Exxon, Firestone, Fotomat Film, Fritos, Gallo Burgundy, Gallo Wines, Gillette Trac II, Goodyear, Hall's Cold Drops, Hamilton Beach, Hanes Panty Hose, Heinz Catsup, J.C. Penney, Jeep, Jello Gelatin, Jello Pudding, Johnson's, Kellogg's Frosted Flakes, Ken-L-Ration, Kentucky Fried Chicken, Kraft, Lava Soap, L'Eggs, Little Friskies, Litton Microwave, Lysol, M&M Candy, Mastercharge, Mazda, Milk, Milwaukee Beer, Mr. Muscle Oven Cleaner, Nestle's Chips, Orange Juice, Oreos, Pabst, Pam, Parkay, Pepsi Light, Perfume by L'Oreal, Pizza Hut, Playtex Girdles, Playtex Panty Hose, Polaroid Pronto, Pringles, Purina Dog Chow, Radio Shack, RC Cola, RCA, Scott Towels, Sears, Sinutab, Snackin' Cake, Snowy Bleach, Solo Dog Food, Special K, Sprite, Volkswagen, Whirlpool]
  - FCB Tape 6, originals with index, 1977 and undated, 301506 (Box 4)
    [Includes Ariz. Highways, Bank of Nevada, Butternut Bread, Campbell's, Cincinnati Enquirer, Clairol, Clorox, Conquel, Cudahy Gelatin, Dial Soap, Equitable Insurance, First Chicago, Foster Farms, Frito Lay, Funks, Hallmark, Hughes Air West, Kraft Dinners, Max Factor, Mazda, Ore-Ida, Pizza Hut, Raid, Safeway, Sears, Speed Queen, Sunbeam, Suzuki, United States Forest Service, Valley National Bank, Winchell's Donut House, Zenith]
  - FCB Tape 7, handwritten without index, undated, 301505 (Box 4)
    [Includes A-1, American Express, Arm & Hammer Detergent, Arrid, Bayer, BC Powder, Belk's, Bounty, Burger King, Calgonite, Care, Carefree Gum, Country Time, Cross Creek Savings and Loan, Digel, Doritos, Eagle Milk, Elmer's Glue-all, ERA (Electronic Realty Associates), Ex-Lax, Exxon, Fixodent, Fleischmann's Margarine, Ford, Freshen-Up, Friskies, Fruit of the Loom, Gaines Burgers, General Motors, Geritol, Gibson, Gravy Train, Grease Relief, Hardee's, Hartz 2-in-1, Heinz, Holiday Inn, Hunt's Catsup, J.C. Penney, Kellogg's, Kimbies, King Kong (movie), Kool Aid, Lucite Paint, Lysol, MacArthur (movie), Mazda GLC, McDonald's, Mercury Cougar, Michelin, Mr. Coffee, Murine II, Nytol, Oil of Olay, One on One (movie), One Step at a Time, Orange Juice, Orkin, Pepsi, Pepsodent, Pine Power, Planter's, Playtex, Polaroid, Prudential, Red Lobster, The Rescuers (movie), Rolaids, Sanka, Schick, Sears, Shake 'n Bake, Shower to Shower, Starkist, Stay Free, Tide, Timex, Town & Country, Triangle Volkswagen, Triumph Spitfire, Tylenol, Volkswagen, Weedeater, Western Auto, Western Electric, White Cloud, Wishbone]
  - FCB Tape 7, originals with index, undated, 301504 (Box 4)
    [Includes A-1, Allstate Insurance, American Express, Arrid, Arm & Hammer Detergent, Bayer, BC Powders, Belk's, Borden Eagle Brand Milk, Bounty, Burger King, Calgonite, CARE, Carefree Sugarless Gum, Country Time Lemonade, Cross Creek Savings, Di-gel, Electrical Realty Associates, Elmer's Glue-All, Ex Lax, Exxon, Fixodent, Fleischmann's Margarine, Florida Orange Juice, Ford, Freshen-Up Gum, Friskies, Fruit of the Loom, Gaines Gravy Train, Gaines Burger, General Motors, Geritol, Gibson Appliance, Grease Relief, Hardee's, Hartz 2 in 1 Collar, Heinz Ketchup, Holiday Inn, Hunt's Catsup, J.C. Penney, Kellogg's Corn Flakes, Kimbies Super Dry, King Kong (movie), Kool Aid, Lucite Paint, Lysol, MacArthur (movie), Mazda GLC, McDonald's, Mercury Cougar, Michelin, Miller Lite, Mr. Coffee, Murine II, Nacho Cheese Doritos, Nytol, Oil of Olay, One on One (movie), Orkin, Pepsi, Pepsodent, Phillips Petroleum, Pine Power, Pizza Hut, Planter's, Playtex, Polaroid One Step, Prudential, Red Lobster, The Rescuers (movie), Rolaids, Sanka, Schick Super II, Sears, Shake 'n Bake, Shower to Shower, Starkist, Stayfree, Tide, Timex, Town and Country, Triange Cars, Triumph Spitfire, Tylenol, Volkswagen, Water Pik Filters, Weedeater, Western Auto, Western Electric, White Cloud, Wishbone Salad Dressing]